Finding Aid for the WSM Radio and Television Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
WSM Radio and Television Collection
1928 - 1966
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0355
5.46 linear feet
Provenance
President of National Life and Accident Insurance Company, the parent company of WSM, Inc., Jesse Wills appreciated the research value of the wide variety of material related to the activities of WSM Radio and TV. In May 1967 he donated to Vanderbilt University an assortment of this material and added to the collection in July 1968. Jesse Wills also donated the Grand Ole Opry Collection, which complements the WSM RADIO_& TV material.
Scope and Content
The WSM RADIO & TV collection is composed of correspondence, photographs, scripts of radio programs, and promotional material. It is stored in thirteen manuscript boxes, eight of which contain scripts of radio programs. Dates of the collection range from 1928 to 1966 with a large portion of the material dated in the 1940s.
WSM Radio is probably best known as the station that broadcasts the Grand Ole Opry. Scripts from Opry broadcasts together with autographs and photographs of Opry stars are among the collection's documents.
During World War II, Variety magazine sponsored a SHOWMANAGEMENT Award. In entries to the contest, WSM Radio outlined its contribution to the "war effort," using photographs to illustrate several points. The Federal Communications Commission Clear Channel Hearings of 1947 also serve as a good profile of WSM Radio during the 1940s.
Chronology
October 5, 1925 First radio broadcast over the National Life and Accident Insurance Company's radio station.
November 28, 1925 The "WSM Barn Dance," forerunner of the Grand Ole Opry is launched.
1927 The "WSM Barn Dance" becomes the Grand Ole Opry.
1932 WSM is awarded a clear channel at 650 kilocycles. Its power is increased from 5,000 watts to 50,000 watts.
November, 1939 The Grand Ole Opry is carried by the NBC Radio Network.
1941 WSM becomes first American commercial frequency modulation radio station, W47NV, a forerunner of WSM-FM.
1943 The Grand Ole Opry moves to the Ryman Auditorium and stays there for the next 31 years.
September 30, 1950 WSM-TV debuts as the first television station in Nashville, building its own microwave relay system to Louisville, KY
1951 "The Waking Crew," the second longest running live radio broadcast, goes on the air under the name, "8 O'clock Time."
1955 "Grand Ole Opry," WSM's first network show, is televised on ABC-TV.
August 29, 1964 WSM-TV becomes the first television station in the United States to receive satellite weather map photos transmitted from NASA's Nimbus satellite.
1965 WSM-TV brings color programming to Nashville.
1968 WSM-FM makes its debut with 100,000 watts.
June 30, 1970 Opryland U.S.A., an amusement park with a musical theme, has its official groundbreaking.
May 27, 1974 Opening of Opryland U.S.A.
March 16, 1974 The Grand Ole Opry moves into the Grand Ole Opry House situated on the grounds at Opryland.
1974 Opryland Productions television and commercial production operation goes into business in the Grand Ole Opry House.
1975 WSM-TV becomes the first Nashville television station to broadcast an hour-long local news program.
November, 1977 The Opryland Hotel, Tennessee's largest convention hotel property, opens.
March A, 1978 The Grand Ole Opry is televsied live over the Public Broadcasting Service annually through 1981.
September, 1980 WSM forms Opry land Radio Productions to produce and market syndicated and network radio programming.
March 11, 1981 NLT Corporation, parent company of WSM, Inc., announces plans for the sale of WSM-TV to make way for WSM's entry into satellite and cable television programming.
September 12, 1981 "Nashville Alive," the first live cable television series to be telecast from Nashville, premieres from the Stagedoor Lounge of the Opryland Hotel, being telecast on WTBS from Atlanta.
November 3, 1981 WSM-TV is sold to Gillett Broadcasting Company and becomes WSMV-TV.
December 8, 1981 WSM and the Associated Press announce the Music Country Network, an overnight satellite radio network, with WSM-AM as the flagship station.
January 19, 1982 WSM announces a venture between Opry land Productions and Group W Satellite Communications for the Nashville Network satellite and cable operation.
- Incoming Correspondence. Andrews-Prevention (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Incoming Correspondence. Sandberg-Woodman (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Outgoing Correspondence, 1944-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- News Releases and Memos., 1942-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Entry to VARIETY Survey of SHOWMANAGEMENT, 1942 (Box 1-5, Folder 1-10)
- Entry for VARIETY Survey of SHOWMANAGEMENT, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Entry for VARIETY Survey of SHOWMANAGEMENT, 1947-Introductory Bookie (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Schedule of Programs, 1928. Holograph. Bottom 1%" cut off book. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Program Release, 1940, 1942, 1943, 1944, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Program Release, 1946, 1947 3-2 Program Release, 1948, 1949 • 3-3 Program Release, 1950-51 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Program Release, miscellaneous issues (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Federal Communications Commission, Clear Channel Hearing, 1947. 4_4_ 4_8 Neilson coverage Service, No. 1. Advance Area Report, 1952 Covering the states of AL, AR, FL, GA, IL, IN, KS, KY, LA, MS, MO, NC, OH, OK, SC, TN, TX, VA, WV 4-9 1956 Neilson Coverage Service (Box 4-1, Folder 4-3)
- ' Our Shield, various issues (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Our Home Office Shield, various issues (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Profile of area covered by WSM radio, [1955] (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Profile of WSM newscasting (Box 4, Folder 13)
- The Mystery Market, [1955?] (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Federal Communications Commission, Broadcast Action, Clear Channels, 14, September 1961 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Scripts for Radio Programs, in alphabetical order (see Register, Appendix #1) (Box 5-1, Folder 5-2)
- Scripts for Radio Programs, in alphabetical order (see Register, Appendix #1) (Box 6-1, Folder 6-6)
- Scripts for Radio Programs, in alphabetical order (see Register, Appendix #1) (Box 7-1, Folder 7-7)
- Scripts for Radio Programs, in alphabetical order (see Register, Appendix #1) (Box 8-1, Folder 8-8)
- Scripts for Radio Programs, in alphabetical order (see Register, Appendix #1) (Box 9-1, Folder 9-6)
- Scripts for Radio Programs, in alphabetical order (see Register, • Appendix #1) (Box 10-1, Folder 10-8)
- Scripts for Radio Programs, in alphabetical order (see Appendix #1) (Box 11-1, Folder 11-6)
- Scripts for Radio Programs, in alphabetical order (see Appendix #2) 12-6 Unidentified Scripts for Radio Programs (Box 12-1, Folder 12-5)
- WSM Background Information, Part I (Box 12, Folder 7)
- WSM Background Information, Part II (Box 12, Folder 8)
- WSM "Facilities" and Policy-Public Service" (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Legal Documents (see Appendix #2) (Box 12, Folder 10)
- History of the Grand Ole Opry (Box 12, Folder 11)
- "Radio School" Survey (Box 12, Folder 12)
- 1965 Disc Jockey Convent ion, Rosters (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Braille Radio News, Vol. 29, no. 10, (October 1963) (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Magazine and Newspaper Articles 13-2 WSM Publications 54 Facts about WSM [1954] Greetings«..to our Noontime Neighborsa If a Tree FalIs It's Noontime Neighbors! [1953] Telephone Directory WSM Television Radio This is Your Guide to Nashville...Music City, U.S.A. [1965] WSM Family Album WSM News Review of 1942 WSM: The Station that Built a City, Music City, U.S.A. WSMpire, (June 1966) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- "Daybook" 18 April, 1966-13 October 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Francis Craig, Articles and Profiles (Box 13, Folder 4)
- WSM Promotiona1 Flyers (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Nat iona 1 LIfe and Trust, Old Guard (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Misce1laneous (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Nashvilie Advert ising Federation, Diamond Award, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Photographs-Boating Party [Old Hickory Lake] (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Photographs-Picnic, [i960] (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Photographs-Phi 1 Harris Homecoming, Nashvi1le, Tennessee (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Photographs-1st Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Photographs-2nd Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Photographs-3rd Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Photographs-4th Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Photographs-Various (Box 13, Folder 16)
- WSM Banner (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Incoming Correspondence
  - A
    - Andrews, Mrs. L.H., 6 Sept 1966
  - C
    - Caldwell, William H., 25 June 1946
    - Calvert, Margaret., 8 Jan 1943
    - Craig, Francis., 19 Feb 1948; 16 Oct, N.D.
  - D
    - Dandridge, E.P. N.D. Denny, Bill. 18 Apr 1966 Doyle, Edrie. 22 Dec 1948 Doyne, George W., 9 Mar 1960
  - E
    - Evons, Raymond., 4 Oct 1964 f
  - F
    - Fielder, Ted M., 4 June 1964
    - Fillebrown, T.S., Jr., 19 Jan 1965
    - Foster, Kendall (Al)., 19 June 1946; 23 July 1946; 6 June, N.D.(telegram); 6 June, N.D. (telegram)
  - G
    - Graham, Bill., 11 Dec 1947
  - K
    - Kirkland, Ellis, Hodson, Chaffetz, & Masters., 31 Mar 1961; 14 Sept 1961
  - M
    - Martin, W.G., 17 June 1946
  - N
    - Nashville Automobile Club., 26 June 1946
  - O
    - Official Films, Inc. N.D.
    - Owens, Martha Patricia., 8 June 1948
  - P
    - Phifer, William E., Jr., 18 Apr 1945
    - Presba, Fellers, and Presba., 19 Apr 1948
    - Prevention of Blindness and Conservation of Vision., 8 Dec 1938; 6 June 1939
  - S
    - Sandberg, Lynn. 15 Feb 1938 Starkoff, Bernard. 11 Apr 1945 Stephens, J. Harold., 9 Apr 1945
  - T
    - Taishoff, Sol., 27 June 1946
    - Thomas, Jean., 21 Mar 1948; 23 Apr 1948; 26 Apr 1948; 17 May 1948; 26 May 1948 Transair. 25 July 1946
  - U
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy. N.D.
  - W
    - Weakley, Mrs. Harry R., [1944]
    - White, Billy., 15 Oct 1947
    - Wilkinson, W.R. N.D.
    - Wilson, Gordon. 25 Oct 1947 Winkler, Thomas R., 38 Aug 1967
    - Woodman, H.A., 20 Mar 1928; 6 Apr 1928; 9 May 1928; 20 June 1928
- 1944
- VARIETY, Jan 27
- 1946
- Charlie Tobias, Apr 9
- [form letter]; June 11, Syd Eiges; June 20, Bill Caldwell, June 11; June 21
- Sol Taishoff; June 25, Sol Taishoff
- Kendall Foster, July 10
- Kendall Foster, L.M. Mac Arthur, Aug 5
- 1947
- Bradford Kress, Feb 17
- Chattanooga Times, Apr 18
- Newsweek; Oct 16, Harry Link; Oct 17, Francis Craig, Oct 1
- 1948
- Presba, Fellers, and Presba, Apr 21
- Nashville Tennessean, May 27
- 1953
- N.D., "Dee Jay"
- 1955
- Flamingo Films, May 4
- 1958
- "Music Vendor", Nov 8
- 1961
- MSgt. William D.' Kirkpatrick, Jan 12
- 1964
- John Langridge; May 7, Johnny Johnson, May 4
- 1942
- Memo, re: AMERICA'S PRAYER MINUTE [1946] (June 21-23], Memo, re: Broadcast from the Idlewild, July 31
- 1947
- News Release, re: Francis Craig, July 1
- 1948
- News Release, re: Award from VARIETY magazine, Mar 19
- 1951
- March, News Release, re: Background information on WSM (December], Christmas Card from National Life and Trust
- 1958
- News Release, re: 7th Annual Country Music Disc Jockey Convention, Oct 13
- News Release, re: 7th Annual Country Music Disc Jockey Convention, Nov 13
- 1961
- Memo, re: Clear channels, Mar 15
- Appendix #1, Scripts for WSM radio programs held in the collection. Dates do not necessarily denote a complete series.
- A.A. (Alcoholics Anonymous) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Adventures That Made America (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Air Mail Pioneers (Box 5, Folder 1)
- American Ace Coffee (Box 5, Folder 1)
- American Education Week, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- American Education Week America's (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Prayer Minute At The Fair (Box 5, Folder 1)
- The Barn Theatre (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Beginnings of Radio in Nashville (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Breakfast Chats (Box 5, Folder 2)
- The Case Against Cancer (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Challenger Jamboree (See The Pleasant Ridge Folks) (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Governor Frank Clement's TV Speech, 8 May 1957 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Defense in Action (Box 5, Folder 4)
- The Dixie Nightcap Dramatic (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Guild Dunlop Challenger Feeds (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Early Days of Radio in Nashville Easter Bellsa (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Farm Safety Drive #1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Fifteen Minutes in Old Vienna (Box 5, Folder 5)
- The Fireside Hour Program (Box 5, Folder 5)
- The First Year (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Quince Follis (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 4-H and Folk Games (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Freedom Theatre (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Friday Night Show (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Grand Ole Opry, 8 Aug 1939-20 Aug 19491 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Grand Ole Opry, 24 Sept 1949-20 May 1950 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Grand Ole Opry, 3 June 1950-31 Mar 1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Grand Ole Opry, 28 Apr 1951-29 Mar 1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Grand Ole Opry, 12 Apr 1952-27 June 1953 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Grand Ole Opry., 5 Dec 1953-3 May 1958 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- He Hath Not Died in Vain (Box 6, Folder 1)
- He Is Risen (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Home (Box 6, Folder 1)
- The Home Towners Quartette (Box 6, Folder 1)
- In Memoriam (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Interview on Acting Career (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Is It The Truth (Box 6, Folder 2)
- It Can Be Done (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Andrew Jackson's Birthday (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Let's Go To Town (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Long, Long Ago With The Old Timers (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Lullaby Time, 13 Dec 1939-5 Jan 1942 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Lullaby Time, 12 Jan 1942-24 June 1942 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Lullaby Time, 1 July 1942-30 Dec 1942 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Lullaby Time, 6 Jan 1943-28 Apr 1943 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Making the Most of It, 6 Mar 1944-1 Dec 1945 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Making the Most of It, 4 Apr 1946-30 Aug 1946 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Minnie Pearl and Maria (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Abe Martin (Box 7, Folder 3)
- The Methodist Church in Nashville (Box 7, Folder 3)
- More than Before (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Morning Percolator (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Morning Reflections, 5 Jan 1939-10 Nov 1939 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Morning Reflections, 11 Nov 1939-30 Dec 1939 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Morning Reflections, 2 Jan 1940-28 Mar 1940 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Morning Reflections, 29 Mar 1940-6 Nov 1948 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Music for Sunday (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Music Games (Box 8, Folder 1)
- The Music Hour (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Must the So-Called I1Have-not" Nations Expand? (Box 8, Folder 1)
- National Grand Ole Opry Week (Box 8, Folder 1)
- National Life Christmas Party (Box 8, Folder 1)
- National Life Christmas Program (Box 8, Folder 1)
- National Life Recreation Program (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Observation Song (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Old Guard Dinner Show (Box 8, Folder 1)
- One Year Later (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Our America (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Picnics (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 9 July 1940-13 Aug 1940 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 15 Aug 1940-19 Sept 1940 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 21 Sept 1940-7 Nov 1940 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 9 Nov 1940-19 Dec 1940 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 2 Jan 1941-8 Feb 1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 13 Feb 1941-2 April 1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 7 April 1941-13 May 1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 28 May 1941-14 July 1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 16 July 1941-1 Sept 1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 3 Sept 1941-31 Oct 1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Pleasant Ridge Folks, 3 Nov 1941-9 Dec 1942, +N.D. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Portrait of Patsy Cline (Box 9, Folder 6)
- A Postcard From You (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Presentation Platter (Box 9, Folder 6)
- The Public Speaks (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Radio Patrol (Box 10, Folder 1)
- River Boat Revels (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Sacred Music (Box 10, Folder 2)
- The Story of Tennessee (Box 10, Folder 2)
- The Story of the Shield (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Sunday Down South (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Sunday Music Hour (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Sunrise Reflections, 21 July 1938-12 Aug 1938 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Sunrise Reflections, 13 Aug 1938-16 Sept 1938 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Sunrise Reflections, 16 Sept 1938-7 Nov 1938 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Sunrise Reflections, 9 Nov 1938-14 Dec 1938 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Sunrise Reflections, 15 Dec 1938-30 Jan 1939 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Sunrise Reflections, 31 Jan 1939-18 Mar 1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Sunrise Reflections, 20 Mar 1939-12 May 1939 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Sunrise Reflections, 15 May 1939-26 June 1939 11-3 Sunrise Reflections, 27 June 1939-18 Aug 1939 11-4 Sunrise Reflections, 21 Aug 1939-25 Sept 1939 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Tales of American Heroes, 27 Sept 1943-24 Nov 1943 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Tales of American Heroes, 25 Nov 1943-3 Mar 1944 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- This is Your Navy (Box 12, Folder 1)
- This...Our Land (Box 12, Folder 1)
- To John, From Mother (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Two in '42 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Unidentified Scripts (see 12-6) (Box 12, Folder 2)
- The Upper Room (Box 12, Folder 2)
- VD Radio Project (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Variety Presentation Script (Box 12, Folder 2)
- The Village Serenaders (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Visitation Evangelism (Box 12, Folder 3)
- George Washington (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Whiz Quiz (Box 12, Folder 4)
- The Worry Hour (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Your Old Friend and Advisor You're the Jury (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Unidentified Scripts (Box 12, Folder 6)
- APPENDIX #2
- Akeman, David "Stringbean"
- Anglin, Jack (see Wells, Kitty)
- Atkins, Chet
- Brasfield, Rod
- Carlisle, Bill
- Carter, June
- Carter, Maybelle
- Cash, Johnny
- Cooper, Stoney
- Copas, Cowboy
- Cousin Jody (see Summey, James C.)
- Cutrer, Thomas
- Dickens, Jimmy
- Flatt, Lester
- Hawkins, Hawkshaw
- Haynes, Inez (see La Dells)
- Hazelwood, Adelaid (see Woods, Del)
- Hill, Eddie
- Husky, Ferlin
- Jackson, Stonewall
- Jones, George
- Jordanaires
- La Dells
- Lance, Helen C. (see La Dells)
- Lonzo and Oscar
- Louvin Brothers
- Martin, Benny
- Monroe, Bill_
- Newman, Jimmy
- Old Hickory Quartet
- Pearl, Minnie
- Pinson, Dolores D. (see La Dells)
- Price, Ray
- Reeves, Jim
- Robbins, Marty
- (?)Scruggs, Earl (see Flatt, Lester)
- Sharpe, Hank (see Old Hickory Quartet)
- Shepard, Jean
- Sununey, James C.
- Snow, Hank
- Stoker, Gordon (see Jordanaires)
- Sullivan, Oscar (see Lonzo and Oscar)
- Temple, Preston (see Louvin Brothers)
- Tubb, Ernest
- Tubb, Justin
- Wagoner, Porter
- Wells, Kitty
- Wilburn, Teddy
- Wood, Del
- Wright, Johnny (see Wells, Kitty)
- Young, Faron
- Photographs-1st Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Photographs-1st Annual Pet Milk Talent Contest (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 1) Audience (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 2) Unidentified pianist, Margie Bowes (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 3) Ken Runyard, Sid Wolf, Bob Cooper(WSM), Tommy Cutrer, Bob Pigg.ott (Pet Milk), Ed Peterson(Keystone), Margie Bowes-front (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 4) Front row: Bob Piggott, Margie Bowes, Tommy Cutrer Back row: 6 unknowns (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 5) Margie Bowes j Bob Piggot^Pet Milk)-center; 6 unknowns (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 6) Bill Sacho(Billboard), Margie Bowes, Sid Wolf (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 7) Bob Cooper(WSM), CHuck Forbes, Margie Bowes, Ken Runyard (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 8) Ed Peterson(Keystons), Emerson Pryor and Nadine Wright(WDVA Danville, Virginia), Tommy Cutrer, Margie Bowes, Sidney Wolfe (Keystone), Bob Piggott(Pet Milk), Ernest Tubb, Champ Humphrey (Gardner), Roy Acuff (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 9) Margie Bowes, Tommy Cutrer, Melba Montgomery (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 10) Front row: unknown, Margie Bowes, Melba Montgomery, Johnny Tillotson. Back Row: 7 unknowns (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 11) Margie Bowes, Bob Piggott(Pet Milk) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 12) Far left: Hank Garland; Margie Bowes-at microphone; Floyd "Lightninl" Chance-bass; Ernest Tubb (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 13) Margie Bowes, Tommy Cutrer, Melba Montgomery (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 14) The Drifters(?), William Harris, Margie Bowes, Glenn Johnson, The Treys (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 15) Ray Edenton-guitar, Margie Bowes, Ernest Tubb, T. Tommy Cutrer (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 16) Pauline Hotze, Tommy Cutrer, Alice Morris (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 17) The Drifters, Floyd "Lightnin'1' Chance-bass, [June Webb?]-guitar (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 18) The Drifters-microphone, Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance-bass, Tommy Cutr (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 19) Unknown-bass, Drifter, Roy Acuff, Drifter, [June Webb?] (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 20) Unknown-bass, Drifters, Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance-bass, [June Webb? (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 21) [Executive's wives](7 women) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 22) [Executive's wives] (2 women) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 23) Group loading bus (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 24) Ray Edenton-guitar, William Harris-microphone, Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance-bass, Roy Acuff (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 25) William Harris, Bob Piggott(Pet Milk) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 26) Ray Edenton-guitar, William Harris-microphone, Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance-bass (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 27) William Harris-microphone, Ray Edenton-guitar, Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance-bass, Bob Piggott(Pet Milk)?, T. Tommy Cutrer (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 28) Hank Garland-guitar, Ray Edenton-guitar, Roy Acuff, William Harris Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance-bass, The Treys, [June Webb?]-guitar (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 29) Emerson Pryor(WDVA), Sid Wolf, Bob Cooper(WSM), T. Tommy Cutrer, Bob Piggott(Pet Milk), Edwin Peterson(Keystone), Front: William Ha (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 30) Center: Glenn Johnson of Rocky Mount, NC (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 31) Sid Wolf, 2 unknowns, Glenn Johnson, Edwin Peterson(Keystone), Bob Cooper(WSM) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 32) Bob Piggott(Pet Milk), Glenn Johnson (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 33) Emerson Pryor(WDVA), Sid Wolf, Bob Cooper(WSM), T. Tommy Cutrer, Bob Piggot t(Pet Milk), Edwin Peterson(Keys tone), in front: Glenn Johnson (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 34) Glenn Johnson at piano (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 35) Glenn Johnson-piano, Ray Edenton-guitar, Floyd "Lightnin" Chance-bass (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 36) Glenn Johnson-piano, Ray Edenton-guitar, Floyd "Lightnin"' Chance-bass, Ernest Tubb (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 37) The Jordanaires (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 38) The La Dells, Pauline Hotze?, unknown, Alice Morris, Ferlin Husky (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 39) 2 Unknowns, Melba Montgomery, Johnny Tillotson, Ed Peterson, Sid Wolf (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 40) 2 Unknowns, Melba Montgomery-seated, Ed Peterson, Sid Wolf, Johnny Tillotson-knee ling (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 41) 2 Unknowns, Melba Montgomery, Bob Piggott(Pet Milk) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 42) Melba Montgomery, 3 unknowns (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 43) Panel: Ernest Tubb, Del Kirkpatrick, Bob Cooper(WSM). Bob Piggott(Pet Milk) Roy Acuff (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 44) Unknown, Bob Piggott(Pet Milk) 2 Unknowns (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 45) Unknown-bass, Howdy Forrester-fiddle, [June Webb?]-guitar, Brother Oswald (Beecher "Pete" Kirby)-guitar, unknown, T. Tommy Cutrer. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 46) Howdy Forrester-fiddle, [June Webb?]-guitar, Roy Acuff, Brother Oswald (Beecher "Pete" Kirby)-guitar. Background: Johnny Ti1lotson-guitar, seated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 47) Unknown woman-guitar, Othell Sul1ivan-guitar, Roy Acuff, Tommy Cutrer (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 48) Johnny Ti1lotson-mic rophone, Floyd "Lightnin" Chance-bass, [June Webb?]-gui 49 Ray Edenton-guitar, Roy Acuff, Johnny Tillotson, [June Webb?]-guitar, Treys( (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 50) Emerson Pryor(WDVA), Sid Wolf, Bob Cooper(WSM) Tommy Cutrer, Bob Piggott (Pet Milk),* Edwin Peterson(Keystone), Front: Johnny Tillotson (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 51) Johnny Tillotson, 2 unknown men looking at magazine (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 52) Johnny Til lotson-guita r, Floyd "Lightnin" Chance-bass, [June Webb?]-guitar (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 53) Johnny Tillotson-guitar, T. Tommy Cutrer-behind music stand (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 54) Emerson Pryor(WDVA), Sid Wolf, Bob Cooper(WSM), Tommy Cutrer, Bob Piggott?-hidden, Edwin Pete r.son(Keys tone) In f ront: The Treys (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 55) Ray Edenton-guitar, The Treys-microphone (Box 13, Folder 12)